let questions=[
	{
		numb:1,
		question:"Which of the following cannot be used as an intermediate code form? ",
		answer:"Quadruples",
		options:[
			"Quadruples",
			"Syntax trees",
			"Three address codes",
			"Post fix notation"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:2,
		question:"Which of the following can be used to identify loops?",
		answer:"All of these",
		options:[
			"Dominators",
			"Reducible graphs",
			"Depth first ordering",
			"All of these"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:3,
		question:"Replacement of an expensive operation by a cheaper one is called",
		answer:"Reduction in strength",
		options:[
			"Reduction in strength",
			"Loop-invariant computation",
			"Code motion",
			"None of these"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:4,
		question:"The cost of developing a compiler is proportional to",
		answer:" All of these",
		options:[
			"Flexibility of the available instruction set",
			"Complexity of the architecture of the target machine",
			"Complexity of the source language",
			" All of these"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:5,
		question:"Which of the following is not a source of error?",
		answer:"None of these",
		options:[
			"Compilers themselves",
			" Faulty algorithm",
			" both a and b",
			"None of these"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:6,
		question:"Loader is a program that",
		answer:"Places programs into memory and prepares them for execution",
		options:[
			"Places programs into memory and prepares them for execution",
			"Automates the translation of assembly language into machine language",
			"Accepts a program written in a high level language and produces an object program",
			"Appears to execute a source program as if it were machine language"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:7,
		question:"Interpreter is preferred over a compiler is",
		answer:"During program development phase",
		options:[
			"When efficient use of computer resources is the consideration",
			"During program development phase",
			"When storage space is to be minimized",
			"All of these"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:8,
		question:"Which of the following is used for grouping of characters into tokens?",
		answer:"Scanner",
		options:[
			"Parser",
			"Code optimizer",
			"Scanner",
			"Code generator"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:9,
		question:"A basic block can be analyzed by",
		answer:" DAG",
		options:[
			"Graph with cycles",
			" DAG",
			" Flow graph",
			"None of these"
		]
	},
	{
		numb:10,
		question:"Type checking is normally done during",
		answer:"Syntax directed translation",
		options:[
			"Code optimization",
			"Lexical analysis",
			"Syntax directed translation",
			"Syntax analysis"
		]
	},
];